Want to clear some space?
Uninstall apps and games you’re not using.
Go to My games and apps.
You can see how much space is available on your Xbox.
Highlight a game or app,
press the Menu button on your controller,
and choose Manage game, or Manage app for apps.
To delete an individual item, highlight it,
press the Menu button,
and then Uninstall.
To uninstall everything, including add-ons and saved data,
select Manage all, then Uninstall all.
After you uninstall something,
you can still find the tile in your collection by scrolling right.
That way it’s easy to reinstall
if you want to use them again later.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.